[
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "自由な、空いている",
    "answer": "libre"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "招待する",
    "answer": "inviter"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "夕食をとる",
    "answer": "dîner"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "一緒に",
    "answer": "ensemble"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "最後の",
    "answer": "dernier"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "部屋、会場",
    "answer": "salle"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "半分",
    "answer": "demi"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "したがって、だから",
    "answer": "donc"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "協定、一致",
    "answer": "accord"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "より少ない",
    "answer": "moins"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "親切な、優しい",
    "answer": "gentil"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "空港",
    "answer": "aéroport"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "助ける",
    "answer": "aider"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "外国人",
    "answer": "étranger"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "閉じる",
    "answer": "fermer"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "窓",
    "answer": "fenêtre"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 11,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "門、戸",
    "answer": "porte"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "バゲットパン、棒",
    "answer": "baguette"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "パン屋",
    "answer": "boulangerie"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "知られた",
    "answer": "connu"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "レモン",
    "answer": "citron"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "選手",
    "answer": "joueur"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "会社、社会",
    "answer": "société"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "走る",
    "answer": "courir"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "飲む",
    "answer": "boire"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "忙しい",
    "answer": "occupé"
  },
  {
    "lesson": 12,
    "category": "単語",
    "topic": "基本単語",
    "type": "fill-in-the-blank",
    "question": "菓子、ケーキ屋",
    "answer": "pâtisserie"
  }
]
